You know, in this day and age, folks really need to be showing resistance resumes.
Like you couldn't just roll up onto the rebel base like, hey, I'm here, I'm down. Like, no,
they have to vet you. They have to be able to see like, okay, what you've been on, et cetera,
et cetera. And I just feel like we got to be demanding of that in the present to be able to
determine who are ops and also like, who's just like in it for the shine or the fame, right?
Because people will just show up out the blue, like I'm down. Power to the people. And you're
like, okay, that sounds good. Show us how. You've always got to be able to show like resistance
referrals. Like I got resistance referrals. You can call Claudia de la Cruz. Okay. I mean,
like there's video proof and a long list of folks that you can call upon to check my transgression
transcript. And it should be the same for all. And you know, we all got to be able to show.
We all got to be able to demonstrate like, this is where I come from. This is what I'm about. So
don't think I just popped out. And there's no ego in that. That's just how it need to be.
Support a real one.
Mm-hmm.